crownpeak.com 2015-05-26

# Privacy

### Introduction

CrownPeak Technology (“CrownPeak”) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following outlines our information gathering and dissemination practices; our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through this website www.crownpeak.com and other websites owned by CrownPeak accessible by our customers’ end users or by the general public. These websites are collectively referred to in this privacy statement as “our website”, “this website” or their respective plurals. Our use of information collected through our website shall be limited to the purposes outlined in the CrownPeak Services Agreement executed between CrownPeak and your company or, in the case of general public access, by the principles outlined in this privacy statement. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy statement and let us know if you have any questions.

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this statement easy to find, we make it available on our corporate website (http://www.crownpeak.com/privacy) and at every point where personal information may be requested.

To show our commitment to privacy, we have entered into three voluntary data privacy programs: the [**US-EU Safe Harbor**](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/), [**U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor**](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/) and [**TRUSTe**](http://www.truste.org/). Our involvement and participation in these programs is described below.

### Safe Harbor

We follow privacy principles with respect to transfers of personal information from the European Economic Area (EEA) (which includes the twenty-eight member states of the European Union (EU) plus Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway) and from Switzerland to the United States.

The United States Department of Commerce and the European Commission have agreed on a set of data protection principles and frequently asked questions to enable U.S. companies to satisfy the requirement under European Union law that adequate protection be given to personal information transferred from the EEA to the United States (the “U.S.-EU Safe Harbor"). The EEA also has recognized the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor as providing adequate data protection (OJ L 45, 15.2.2001, p.47).

The United States Department of Commerce and the Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) of Switzerland have agreed on a similar set of principles and frequently asked questions to enable U.S. companies to satisfy the requirement under Swiss law that adequate protection be given to personal information transferred from Switzerland to the United States (the “U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor”).

CrownPeak complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. CrownPeak has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view CrownPeak’s certification, please visit [**http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/**](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

In compliance with the Principles, we commit to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information.

### TRUSTe Dispute Resolution

As part of our participation in the Safe Harbor Frameworks, we have agreed to TRUSTe dispute resolution for disputes relating to our compliance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Frameworks. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, you should first contact [**privacy@crownpeak.com**](mailto:privacy@crownpeak.com). If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may raise your complaint with TRUSTe by [**clicking here**](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) , or by fax at 415-520-3420 or mail to TRUSTe Safe Harbor Compliance Dept., [**click for mailing address**](http://www.truste.com/about-TRUSTe/contact-us).

If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of company, the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the company. For information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe's dispute resolution process, click [**here**](http://www.truste.com/products-and-services/dispute-resolution-services/) or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the addresses listed above. The TRUSTe dispute resolution process shall be conducted in English. For human resources data we have agreed to cooperate with Data Protection Authorities.

### TRUSTe Privacy Seal

In addition, CrownPeak has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [**TRUSTe Cloud Privacy program requirements**](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/TRUSTed-cloud/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. The TRUSTe program covers the collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website and our CMS Platform. The use of information collected through these services shall be limited either by the terms agreed to in contract between CrownPeak and its customers or as directly described in this privacy policy.

### The Information We Collect

Our website does not automatically collect personal information from your computer without you voluntarily providing this information. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our website.

We also collect non-personal information, that is, data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may use non-personal information to compile and analyze website usage trends, effectiveness of marketing content or other marketing-related analysis.

For users of the CrownPeak CMS Platform, we collect personal information about you when you set up your account profile to access the service. This information includes details such as your full name, your eMail address, your phone number etc.

Part of CrownPeak’s business also involves hosting websites on behalf of its customers. Some of these websites collect personally identifying information. In these cases, the nature and use of the personally-identifying information collected is determined by the CrownPeak customer.

### Customer Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our website which may contain personal information. We will obtain your consent prior to posting your name, your testimonial, or any other personal information. To request removal of your personal information from our testimonials, contact us at [**privacy@crownpeak.com**](mailto:privacy@crownpeak.com).

### Public Forums

Our web site offers publicly accessible blogs and community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog, customer testimonials or community forum, contact us at privacy@crownpeak.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Social Media (Features) and Widgets

Our web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Access to Personal Information

If your personal information previously collected on our website changes, you may correct, delete inaccuracies, or update this information directly by logging into the website where that information is maintained. We will respond to your access request within 30 days.

If you choose to contact us to request that changes be made on your behalf, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity using the personal information you have previously supplied before granting access or making corrections.

You may also request deletion of your personal information by contacting us as described below under “How to Contact Us”.

### The Way We Use Information

We use the information we collect about you to authenticate your identity when you access our website. This ensures that the information we maintain on your behalf is accessible only to you or to the other members of your company who are authorized to access the same information. We also use the information you provide to respond to your inquiries regarding a demonstration of our products or training registration.

We use your Email address to respond to requests you submit through our website or to communicate alerts and notifications that form part of the normal CrownPeak CMS Platform functionality. We also use your Email address and/or phone number to respond to requests you submit for information through our website.

We never use or share the personal information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. We will not sell your personal information to third parties.

Our service providers will not market to you independently.

It may be necessary - by law, legal process, litigation, subpoena, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence - for us to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect our operations or those of our customers, and to protect your safety or the safety of others. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any third party with your prior consent to do so.

If we engage a third party to process your data on our behalf or to send emails out on our behalf, those third parties will also be bound by our privacy statement.

### Information Related to Data Collected on the CrownPeak CMS Platform

CrownPeak collects personal information to identify individuals and manage their access to the CMS Platform.

CrownPeak will retain personal information we collect on the CMS Platform for as long as needed to provide services to our customers and/or as long as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We collect information for our clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use of our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly and CrownPeak has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct,amend or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the CrownPeak’s Client (the data controller). If the Client request CrownPeak to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 days.

### External Links

Our websites contains links to third party sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third party sites. We are not responsible for information given to us that you authorize for transfer to third party sites. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Website you visit.

### Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

CrownPeak uses secure sockets layer (SSL) for securing communications and transactions across the Internet .  When you enter sensitive information (such as cloud login credentials) we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology. The SSL protocol uses digital certificates to create and secure confidential communications between the browser and our web server. Data transmitted over an SSL connection cannot be tampered with or forged without the two parties (you and CrownPeak) becoming immediately aware of the tampering. A key or padlock icon in the browser window identifies the security mode of most popular browsers. When the browser is running in “normal” mode, the key is broken or the padlock is open. Once an SSL connection has been established, the key becomes whole, or the padlock becomes closed, indicating that the browser is now in “secure” mode. SSL is supported in the vast majority of browsers, which means that almost anyone with a browser can benefit from SSL encryption. CrownPeak uses certificates from well known providers of digital trust services that enable businesses and consumers to engage in commerce and communications with confidence.

For data collected by websites hosted by CrownPeak on behalf of its customers, CrownPeak ensures that all applicable Safe Harbor Principles are applied to the data for as long as it is hosted by CrownPeak and under CrownPeak’s control.

### Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important to us. For that reason, no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 18 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18.

### Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by CrownPeak Technology and our partners (e.g. marketing partners), affiliates, or analytics or service providers  (e.g. marketing automation, analytics, CRM). These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for web analytics and marketing automation, to track user behavior across our site, deliver personalized content, grant access to specific content, and to streamline the process for resource downloads _._ Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

### Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. 

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve and enable services we offer you, marketing, analytics, product functionality, and website functionality. ****

### Flash LSOs

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as Flash to collect and store information. To manage Flash LSOs please click here:

_[**http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html**](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html)_

### Local Storage Objects (HTML5)

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. ****

### Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [**here**](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union, click [**here**](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. ****

**Service Provider, Sub-Processors/Onward Transfer**

CrownPeak may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this privacy policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Licensees. If we engage a third party to process your data on our behalf, that third party will also be bound by our privacy policy.

### Data Retention

CrownPeak will retain the personal data we collect from you for as long as needed to provide services to our customers or to support our own marketing programs as described above. CrownPeak will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Material Change

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### How To Contact Us

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy statement or any other aspect of our privacy or security practices, please contact us at [**privacy@crownpeak.com**](mailto:privacy@crownpeak.com) or send a letter via postal mail to:

Privacy Officer  
CrownPeak Technology  
5880 W. Jefferson Blvd., Studio G  
Los Angeles, CA 90016  
United States of America

We will respond to your questions or complaints within 30 days of our receipt. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [**TRUSTe here**](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

Effective December 19, 2014

* * *

The CrownPeak web site is provided by CrownPeak technology on an "as is" basis. CrownPeak makes no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of this web site or the information, content, materials, or products included on this web site. To the full extent permissible by applicable law, CrownPeak disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement.

Although CrownPeak has attempted to provide accurate information on the CrownPeak Web site, CrownPeak assumes no responsibility for the accuracy or completeness of the information. CrownPeak may change the function or subject matter of the CrownPeak Web site at any time without notice.
